

## **About**

Strong data analysis, data structures, and algorithm skills.

Expertise in JavaScript, both Vanilla JS and frameworks like React, along with TypeScript and OOP principles.

Extensive experience in web development frameworks (NodeJS, React), Java (Spring MVC, Spring Boot), and database management (MySOL, PostgreSOL, MongoDB).

Customer experiences: customer requirement, Business Analyst, technical analysis.

Very strong Web Development: Vanilla JS, TypeScript, OOP, prototype, HTML, CSS

Have a good knowledge UML Design, Modeling Design, DataBase Schemas

Expected Job: Web Dev (Java - J2EE, Spring Boot), FullStack Web dev (JavaScript - NodeJS, React,

HTML, CSS, jQuery), Geometry Map (draw line, polygon, marker, direction)

Slogan: Nothing is impossible.

## **Summary**

Java: Java Core, OOP, Design Pattern, Spring Boot, Maven

Frontend HTML/Javascript/CSS: Vanilla JS, OOP, Prototype, Bootstrap, OpenLayers, CSS Less, SASS, React Js, React Native.

Node JS: OOP, Decorator Reflect MetaData, Electron, Express.js, Nest.js, Cluster, PM2, Puppeteer,

Webpack, Gulp

DataBase: MySql, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

WebRTC: MediaSoup, Kamailio Server, Asterisk Server, FreeSwitch, FFMPEG

Load balancers: Keepalived, HAProxy, NginX, Apache2, Redis catching, Redis Pub/Sub, NATs, RabbitMQ

OS: Windows, MAC OS X, Linux Fedora, Ubuntu, Pop!\_OS, Debian, CentOS

Other Tools: Docker, Git, Redmine, Svn, Jira, Docker, Rancher, Jenkins

nguyendang:2024 1/3

Skill	
Node JS (9/10)	HTML (9/10)
CSS, LESS, SASS (9/10)	PostgreSQL (8/10)
Java (8/10)	MongoDB (7/10)
Kubernet (5/10)	Linux (7/10)

# **Experience**

## Fullstack Node.js Developer

Freelancer · remote

Jun 2024 - Present

# Beings (1 months)

Role: Fullstack Node.js

Create innovative software businesses use for customer & market research. All note-taking & analysis for

Backend: Nodes.js - Nest.js, graphgl, typeorm, MySgl

Frontend: React.is

## Standage Itd (3 months)

Role: FUllstack Node.js

Standage DigiTrad is a trade digital transformation platform that improves efficiency and digitalizes

business processes, allowing trade operations to proceed more quickly and smoothly

Backend: Nodes.js - Nest.js, typeorm, Postgres

Frontend: React.js, Chart.js

# Software Engineer

**VNPT IT** · Full-time

Jan 2021 - Sep 2024 · 3 yrs 8 mos

### GoMeet

Role: Team Leader

- GoMeet - is a high-quality video calling app designed to help you have meaningful and fun interactions with your friends, family, colleagues, and classmates, wherever they are. It's the only app that has communities, events, chats, share files, meetings, presetating in one place.

Languages and technologies:

- Backend: NodeJS Microservice Express.JS, Socket.io, MediaSoup Server, Redis, MongoDB, NATs.
- Frontend: Angular, React.JS, Socket.IO client, MediaSoup Client.

### **Live Stream Server**

Role: Team Leader

Create web client capture screen and live stream to RTMP Server such as Youtube, Facebook or any other CDN LiveStreaming Server

Create client record with headless browser join to the meeting such as Google Meet, Zoom, Microsoft Teams ...

Languages and technologies: Node.js, Puppeteer, XVFB, FFMPEG

## **VCP - Video Call Platform**

Role: R&D (work independent)

- R&D learning about VOIP Server
- Build Call Center system with Asterisk Server, Kamailio Server.

#### **iOMS**

Role: Software Developer

VNPT iQMS provides complete solutions for the entire process of appointment booking - payment - ticket collection - reception - quality assessment and supports information setup for units/hospitals.

Languages and technologies: Java Spring Boot, Spring Security, Hibernate, Mongodb, Log4j, Kafka, Swagger, Lombok, redis, MQTT, Node.js - Electron

### Senior Software Engineer

Evolus VN · Full-time

nguyendang:2024 2/3

Nov 2017 - Feb 2021 · 3 yrs 2 mos

### **NBC Sport Engine**

Role: Fullstack Java Web Developer

- NBC Sport Engine Club team manage student registration, Lesson classes training and competition, Business analytics, statistic report.
- Java: Write services api for mobile and web. Connect database (PostgreSql), aggregate data response JSON data.
- JavaScript/HTML/CSS: Vanilla JS prototype component, HTML flex-box layout, Less CSS.
- Others: Node JS: Express JS + React JS + Gulp Babel

## Software Developer

NEC VN · Full-time

Nov 2014 - Aug 2017 · 2 yrs 8 mos

# **Waseda University**

Role: Web developer for both front-end and back-end

- Java: Spring Frameworks, Velocity, myBatis
- Front-end: jQuery, Ajax, Angular, Cordova
- Self-learning: Python, Django, Angular, TypeScript, NativeScript

### Web Developer

ESI Tech, Vietnam · Full-time

May 2013 - Sep 2014 · 1 yrs 4 mos

Role: Software Developer

Write JavaScript, jQuery, transform XML with XSLT file, draw chart with highchart, Map API (OpenLayers,

Google Map), jQuery pages with JSON data

Environment: Linux (Oracle Linux, Fedora 18/19/20).

# **My Free Time Projects**

#### **Media Monitor**

## https://github.com/dragonfly6373/media-monitor

There is a demo where you can live streaming on Youtube or any RTMP Server, or record any web session to media file and playback

# Logger JS

## https://github.com/dragonfly6373/logger-js

Write node backend log to file and console 4 different levels of logging in a specific order: 'errror', 'warn', 'info', 'debug'

#### **Font Icons**

## https://github.com/dragonfly6373/font-icons

Python Script create font icons file from svgs. Output: myfont-icons.afm, myfont-icons.eot, myfont-icons.woff, myfont-icons.ttf, myfont-icons.woff2

## Education

## **Water Resources University**

Engineers's degree, Information Technology Sep 2008 - Dec 2012

Grade: Good

#### **TOEIC**

English - Communication

Grade: 545

## **Activity**









Reading Book

nguyendang:2024 3/3